A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Secretary of Administration and Finance, 1976-1985.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files, 1978-1984 (Accession 32883)., Extent: 8 cubic feet (8 boxes)
  - Virginia State Retirement System (VSRS) - Meetings, 1984. (Box 2)
  - Advisory Board of Economists - Replies, 1983. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board of Economists - Meeting, 1983 Oct 19. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board of Economists - Ongoing, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board of Economists - Revenue Forecast, 1981 Oct 23. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board of Economists, 1981. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board of Economists, 1980 Aug-Oct. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board of Economists, 1979. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board of Economists - Ongoing, 1977-1978. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates - Meeting, 1982 Oct 18. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates - Meeting, 1982 Dec 7. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates - Meeting, 1981 Dec 3. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates - Meeting, 1980 Dec 9. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates - Meeting, 1979 Nov 16. (Box 3)
  - Advisory Board on Revenue Estimates, 1978. (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth's Intergovernmental Revenue Process (A-95), 1984. (Box 4)
  - Health Care Cost Containments - Central Accounting, 1984. (Box 4)
  - National Association of State Budget Officers, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Administration and Finance - Issue papers and studies, 1983-1984. (Box 4)
  - Administration and Finance - Directive - Prohibiting Use of Legal Size Paper, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Administration and Finance - Directives, 1981-1982. (Box 4)
  - Administration and Finance - Directives, 1980. (Box 4)
  - Administration and Finance - Directives, 1978-1979. (Box 4)
  - Assistant Secretary for Financial Policy, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Census figures, 1980. (Box 4)
  - Census Bureau (Virginia State Data Center Program), 1980. (Box 4)
  - Commission on Block Grants (Executive Order 5 - Robb), 1982. (Box 4)
  - Block Grants, 1982-1984. (Box 4)
  - Manpower Control Program, 1982-1983. (Box 4)
  - Employee Position Report - Ongoing, 1982-1984. (Box 4)
  - MUP Quarterly Position Report - Quarter Ending March 31, 1982, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Employee Position Reports, 1981. (Box 4)
  - Executive Progress Reports - Quarterly Report MUP, 1980 Sept 30. (Box 4)
  - Executive Progress Reports, 1980. (Box 4)
  - Executive Progress Reports, 1979. (Box 4)
  - Executive Progress Reports, 1978. (Box 4)
  - Executive Agreements, 1982-1984. (Box 4)
  - Executive Agreement - Education, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Governor's Plan for Elimination / Competition, 1980. (Box 5)
  - Governor's Cabinet Study, 1978. (Box 5)
  - Delegation of Governor's Signing Authority, 1979. (Box 5)
  - Searing-In Ceremony, 1982 Jan 18. (Box 5)
  - Governor's Office / Cabinet Turnover, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Cabinet Retreat, 1984 July 12-13. (Box 5)
  - Governor's Guidance for 1984-1986, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Editors Luncheons with Governor, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Governor-elect Robb, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Governor's Speeches and Remarks, 1980. (Box 5)
  - James Monroe Memorial Foundation - Payment for special counsel, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Governor's Discretionary Fund, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Governor's Citizen Conference, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Critical Reevaluation Conference, 1983 Sept 23-24. (Box 5)
  - Critical Reevaluation Conference, 1983 June 14. (Box 5)
  - Critical Reevaluation Conference, 1983 May 13. (Box 5)
  - Reevaluating State Government Conference, 1983 Mar 31-Apr 1. (Box 5)
  - Critical Reevaluation Policy Papers, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Governor's Initiatives on Role of State Government, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Review of Cash Management by Private Consultant, 1980. (Box 6)
  - Cash Management - Disbursement Processing Project, 1980. (Box 6)
  - Cash Management - Remittance Processing, 1980-1982. (Box 6)
  - Cash Management Task Force, 1981-1982. (Box 6)
  - Cash Management, 1984. (Box 6)
  - Deferred Compensation Commission, 1981, 1982, 1984. (Box 6)
  - Capital Outlay Process Study, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Consolidated Health Care Data Pay Study (Health Dept.), 1984. (Box 7)
  - Central Accounting, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Executive Development Institute, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Virginia Executive Development Institute, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Federal Budget, 1984. (Box 7)
  - General Assembly correspondence, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Fellows, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Office memos, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Governor's Office correspondence, 1984. (Box 7)
  - Blanket Surety Bonds and Workmen's Compsation Insurance Plan, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Circuit Court Clerks Study - Salary Plans, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Comparable Worth Seminar, 1984 Oct. (Box 8)
  - Comparable Worth Study (HJR 35), 1984. (Box 8)
  - Compensation Board - Constitutional Officers' Funding, 1981-1982. (Box 8)
  - Deputy Sheriffs Salary Study, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - State Energy Plan, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Federal Budget, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Governor's Fellows Program, 1983. (Box 8)
  - National Tax Association / Tax Institute of America - Conference, 1983 Oct. (Box 8)
  - Statistical Coordination Advisory Committee, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - State's Fund Structure - Proposed Changes, 1983-1984. (Box 8)
  - Salary Plan - Sheriff Deputies and other employees (TEFRA), 1983. (Box 8)
  - Yorktown Bicentennial Celebration, 1981 Oct. (Box 8)
- Correspondence and subject files, 1981-1985 (Accession 32968)., Extent: 10 cubic feet (10 boxes)
  - General Assembly, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Bills not signed by Governor, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Memo to Secretary from Ray Sorrell re: 1983 Legislation requiring amendments, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Tax Bills, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Bills to Follow, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Secretary's Daily Legislative Report, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Design - Build Legislation, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Legislative Impact Statements, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Studies to be submitted, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Proposed legislation, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly: Higher Education Revenue Bond Issue, 1983. (Box 1)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Budget Amendments to 1982-1984 Budget, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Amendment Language Indirect Costs (SCHE), 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Budget Reductions (1983 Session), 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: 5% Reduction FY83, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Attorney General Opinion on Inconsistency, 1983 July. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Supplement, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Administration and Finance Budget Amendments, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Amendments - General correspondence, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Governor's Amendments to HB 30 - Veto Session, 1983 Apr 6. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Revised Revenue Forecast, 1983 Feb 4. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Pending Budget Amendments, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Meeting with Governor Robb, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Revenue Windfalls, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Secretary Comments on H/S Amendments, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: House Appropriations Committee - Subcommittee Reports, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Data provided to Senate Finance Committee, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Information to House Appropriations Committee, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Budget Process, 1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Revenue Forecasting, 1982-1983. (Box 2)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Budget for Secretaries, 1982. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Governor's letter of transmittal to the General Assembly, 1982. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Administration and Finance Budget Presentation, 1982. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Budget Amendment, 1982. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Senate Budget Amendments proposed by Governor Robb, 1982. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Governor's Press Briefing, 1982 Jan 11. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Capital Outlay, 1982. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: House Bill 31, 1982. (Box 3)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Committee of Conference - House Bill 30, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Revenue Projections - Six Years, 1981. (Box 4)
  - Revised Revenue Reporting Format, 1984. (Box 4)
  - Revised Estimates, 1982-1984. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Estimates, 1980-1982. (Box 4)
  - Revenue and Expenditure Projections, 1979. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Data Monthly Distribution, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Data, 1983 Dec. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Data, 1983 Nov. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Data, 1983 Oct. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Data, 1983 Sept. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Data, 1983 July-Aug. (Box 4)
  - Revenue Data Monthly Distribution, 1983. (Box 4)
  - General Fund Revenue Forecast (1983-1986), 1983. (Box 4)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation: Board of Trustees meeting, 1985 Dec 6. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1985. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation: Board of Trustees meeting, 1985 Sept 16. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, undated. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation: Corporation, 1985. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation: Godspeed, undated. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1984. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1983. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation: Board of Trustees meeting, 1983 Apr 1. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1982. (Box 5)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1981. (Box 5)
  - General Assembly: House Bill 30, 1983. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly: Required Studies, 1983. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly: Governor's Amendment Notebook, 1983. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly: Budget Data, 1983. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly: January Revenue Collections, 1983. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly: Committee Conference on Budget, 1983. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly: Analysis of Amendments to HB 30, 1983. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly: Senate Amendments to HB 30, 1983. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly: House Amendments to HB 30, 198. (Box 6)
  - State Agencies (A-Hi), 1984. (Box 7)
  - State Agencies (Hi-W), 1984. (Box 8)
  - Speeches (Connock): Commonwealth Planning and Budgeting Process, 1985. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Richmond CPAs, 1984 Dec 18. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Conference on Higher Education, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Virginia Retail Merchants' Association, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): State Chamber Policy Advisory Committee meeting, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): National Association of State Auditors, Comptrollers and Treasurers (NASACT), 1984 Nov 13. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Virginia Municipal League, 1984 Oct 2. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): GMI Industrial Policy Board, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Governor's Fellows, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): SCHEV Budget Conference, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): National Tax Association - Tax Institute of America (NAT-TIA) - Symposium, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Virginia Executive Institute, 1983 May. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Virginia Executive Institute, 1984 May. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Winchester Rotary Club, 1984. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Virginia Legislative Institute, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Virginia Executive Institute, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Forum Club, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Statistical Coordination Advisory Committee, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Virginia Community College Association - Annual meeting, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Senior Business Officers - VMI, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): FEI, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): NATA Conference on Revenue Estimating, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Local Government Advisory Council, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Dealers Banking Association, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Delegate Philpott - Speaker of the House, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Institute for Municipal Officers, 1980. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock): Legislative Assistants Program, 1980. (Box 9)
  - Speeches (Connock), 1979-1982. (Box 9)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Status - Required inclusions budget, 1982. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Budget Language Amendment Transfers, 1982. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: House Bill 30, 1982. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Budget Summaries, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Press Briefings, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Budget Language, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Capital Outlay, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: MUP Targets - 1982-1984 Biennium, 1982. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Targeting, 1982-1984. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Amendments to Budget, 1981. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: House Bill 32 Amendments to 1980-1982 Appropriations Act, 1982. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: General, 1982. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Subcommittee Reports (House Appropriations), 1982. (Box 10)
  - General Assembly / Budget 1982-1984: Capital Outlay Tour, 1982. (Box 10)
- Correspondence and subject files, 1978-1982 (Accession 33039)., Extent: 20 cubic feet (20 boxes)
  - Agribusiness Council, Virginia, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Appropriations Act adjustments, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Attorney General, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, and Air Pollution Control Board, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Black grants, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Board of Elections, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Computer Services, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Comptroller, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Consultants, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Disaster Recovery Assistance, 1982. (Box 1)
  - Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 1)
  - General Services, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 1)
  - House Appropriations Committee, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Indirect costs, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1982. (Box 2)
  - Local Government, Commission on, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Legislative Proposals - Administration and Finance, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Legislation, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Legislative implementation reports, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Liaison Office, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 2)
  - National Governors Association, 1982. (Box 2)
  - Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Planning and Budget, Dept. of - PROBUD, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Public Building Authority, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Public Buildings Commission, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Purchase and Supply, Div. of, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Research Center, Greater Washington, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Savings Bond Campaign, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Senate Finance Committee, 1982. (Box 3)
  - State Finance Committee meeting, 1982 May. (Box 3)
  - State Internal Auditor, 1982. (Box 3)
  - State Senior Business Officers, Council of, 1982. (Box 3)
  - State Planning Agencies, Council of, 1982. (Box 3)
  - State Sheriff's Assocition, Virginia, 1982. (Box 3)
  - Taxation, Dept. of - Bank Stock, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Treasury, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Telecommunications, 1982. (Box 4)
  - United Way Campaign, 1982. (Box 4)
  - VEPCO, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Vendors, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Veterans Cemetery, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Vietnam Veterans Leadership Program, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Waste Sites, Hazardous, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Virginia War Memorial Commission, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Worker's Compensation - Risk Managements, 1982. (Box 4)
  - Manpower Utilization Program, 1978-1980. (Box 5)
  - Higher Education, 1981. (Box 5)
  - Legislation, 1980-1981. (Box 5)
  - Legislative implementation report, 1981. (Box 5)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1981. (Box 5)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1981. (Box 5)
  - Criminal Justice Services Commission, 1981. (Box 5)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1980-1981. (Box 5)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 1981. (Box 5)
  - United Way, 1981. (Box 5)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science (William and Mary), 1981. (Box 5)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority, 1980-1981. (Box 5)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 1980. (Box 5)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1980. (Box 5)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science - Audit, 1980. (Box 5)
  - Appalachian Power, 1977-1978. (Box 5)
  - VEPCO, 1976-1979. (Box 5)
  - Year End Balance, 1981-1982. (Box 6)
  - Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of - Christopher Newport College, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Motor Vehicle, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Health, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Council of Higher Education, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1979-1982. (Box 6)
  - George Mason University, Longwood College, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Old Dominion University, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Mary Washington College, Norfolk State University, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Highways and Transportation, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Radford University, State Police, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Transportation Safety, Dept. of, 1982. (Box 6)
  - University of Virginia, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Military Institute, Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Community College System, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Employment Commission, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Virginia State University, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Virginia Port Authority, Virginia State Library and Archives, 1982. (Box 6)
  - War Veterans Claims, 1982. (Box 6)
  - College of William and Mary, 1982. (Box 6)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1983 July. (Box 7)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1983 Aug. (Box 7)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1983 Sept. (Box 7)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1983 Oct. (Box 7)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1983 Nov. (Box 7)
  - Governor's News Summaries, 1983 Dec. (Box 7)
  - Agribusiness Council, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Asbestos, 1978-1981. (Box 8)
  - ASPA, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Capitol Budget Hearings, 1983 Apr. (Box 8)
  - Capitol Budget Presentations, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Capital Outlay - General, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Capital Outlay Projects, 1982-1984. (Box 8)
  - Capital Outlay Progress Reports, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Capital Outlay Subcommittee, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Cheatham Annex, 1979-1981. (Box 8)
  - Commission on Block Grants, 1982-1983. (Box 8)
  - Congressional Delegation, 1983 June 22. (Box 8)
  - Congressional Delegation, 1983 Jan 11. (Box 8)
  - Consultants - General, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Council of State Planning Agencies, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Energy conservation, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Emergency regulations, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Federal budget analysis, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Federal Executive Institute, 1982. (Box 8)
  - General Services Administration, U.S., 1983. (Box 8)
  - Governmental Accounting Standards Board, 1981. (Box 8)
  - General Assembly - Tax legislation, 1982. (Box 8)
  - General Assembly - Special Session cost, 1980-1981. (Box 8)
  - General Assembly - Pay and benefits, 1983. (Box 8)
  - General Assembly - Member correspondence, 1982-1983. (Box 8)
  - Governmental Employees Association, Virginia, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Governor Robb - Press releases, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Governor's Fellows, 1982-1983. (Box 8)
  - Governor - Exemption on sales tax on food, 1982. (Box 8)
  - Governor's Economic Advisory Council, 1983. (Box 8)
  - Governor - Monthly reports to, 1981-1983. (Box 9)
  - Governor - Responses, 1981-1983. (Box 9)
  - Governor - HR responses, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Governor - Transportation responses, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Governor's targets, 1982. (Box 9)
  - House Appropriations Committee, 1982. (Box 9)
  - House Appropriations Committee, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Implementation reports, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission (JLARC), 1983. (Box 9)
  - Kepone, 1983. (Box 9)
  - Emergency Services, State Office of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Employment Commission, Virginia, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Governor's Employment and Training Council, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Health, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Health, Dept. of - Medicaid Program, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Highways and Transportation, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Housing and Community Development, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Industrial Development, Division of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Lieutenant Governor, Office of the, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Port Authority, Virginia, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Social Services, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Supreme Court of Virginia, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Virginia State Library, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Virginia Institute of Marine Science, 1983. (Box 10)
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1983. (Box 10)
  - War Veterans' Claims, Division of, 1983. (Box 10)
  - VEPCO and Appalachian Power negotiation, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Job Partnership and Training Act, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Business Report, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Juvenile Justice and Deliquency Prevention Advisory Council, 1982. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Public Building Authority, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Town and City, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Volunteer Fire Dept. and Rescue Squad Members Study, 1981. (Box 11)
  - Conversion of GAAP Basis financial statements, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Year End balances, 1982-1983. (Box 11)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept of, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Arts, Commission for the, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Attorney General, Office of the, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Block Grants, Advisory Committee on Education, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Community College System, Virginia, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Corrections, Dept. of, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Education, Dept. of (State Board of Education), 1983. (Box 11)
  - Higher Education, Council of (The Virginia Plan), 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind, 1983. (Box 11)
  - George Mason Univerity, 1983. (Box 11)
  - J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Norfolk State University, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Old Dominion University, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Radford University, 1983. (Box 11)
  - University of Virginia, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University - School of Business Advisory Board, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Military Institute, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Virginia State University, 1983. (Box 11)
  - William and Mary, College of, 1983. (Box 11)
  - Administration and Finance, Secretary of - Office organization, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Administration and Finance, Secretary of - Agency head meetings, 1982. (Box 12)
  - Administration and Finance, Secretary of - Agency quarterly objective reports, 1982-1984. (Box 12)
  - Compensation Board, 1983. (Box 12)